<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<monsterfeed xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <createddate>10/30/2015 1:41:06 AM</createddate>
  <totaljobs>30604</totaljobs>
  <jobs>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>152154121</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[C UNIX Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Creates and modifies C programs by converting project requirements into C code.  Duties:  * Confirms project requirements by reviewing program objective, input data, and output requirements with analyst, supervisor, and client.  * Encodes project requirements by converting work flow information into computer language.  * Programs the computer by entering coded information.  * Confirms program operation by conducting tests; modifying program sequence and/or codes.  * Prepares reference for users by writing operating instructions.  * Maintains historical records by documenting program development and revisions.  * Maintains client confidence and protects operations by keeping information confidential.  * Ensures operation of equipment by following]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[BCforward]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/09/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/08/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=152154121&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156281167</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Looking for Mini CTO's who solve BIG Technology Problems (up to 250K)]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Whether you are a senior software engineer or a hands-on CTO, this Boston based, software product company needs someone like you to help with every aspect of enterprise application integration. This user friendly platform performs all types of functions, from data analysis to parallel processing. This position is perfect for any tech passionate, travel enthusiast looking for that next step in their career. When you’re not facing off with clients, you’re working out of your home office and can be located anywhere in the United States.  REQUIREMENTS:  Computer Science Degree (or related)  Excellent written and verbal communication skills  5+ years]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Gambit Technologies Inc]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/28/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156281167&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156624889</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Remote === Cisco Network Engineer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cisco Network Engineer with focus on Cisco centric Data Centers  This is a REMOTE-TELECOMMUTE Contract role  Ideal candidate has remote--telecommuting--work from home Experience and is in the Eastern (EST) time zone  Candidates outside of EST time Zone by 1 hour will be considered  Candidates should have either CCNP or CCIE  Must have experience in designing and implementing WAN with MPLS and VPN tunnels. Implemented DMVPN. Working experience in Cisco Nexus Switch. EIGRP, BGP, OSPF, Cisco ISE, FireSight, ASA firewall, QoS, Cisco Prime.  PLUS’s or Nice to have - Cisco UC, CM, Unity  Project:  Design and Implement Highly Redundant WAN, Network]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[The G and S Technology Group Inc]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/14/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/13/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156624889&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157338920</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Adobe AEM Sr Developer for Bonita Springs, Florida]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Title: Adobe AEM Sr Developer  Location: Florida (Bonita Springs)  Minimum Experience Required: 5-8 YEARS  Mandatory Skills: Adobe AEM  Desirable Skills: HTML, JavaScript, CSS  Required Skills:  Proficiency and solid track record of working with marketing automation tools for campaign management.  Hands on ability and experience in configuring Adobe Campaign, Eloqua, or similar campaign management tool. Certification is a plus.  Minimum 3+ years of experience deploying marketing automation campaigns for real world marketing initiative  Experience in developing A/B testing and campaign optimization  HTML/CSS/Javascript  Ability to work with both marketing personnel and IT  Ability to write clear business requirements documentation and functional specs]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Terminal Contacts]]></companyname>
      <activedate>09/23/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/22/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Bonita Springs</city>
        <state>FL</state>
        <zip>34133</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157338920&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157706428</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Information Technology Specialist]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Everything begins with solid communications. And in this hyper-networked world, that won't change anytime soon. So set yourself up in a promising civilian career by learning the Information Technology skills you need in the Army National Guard.  Computers are essential to every division of the military. In the Army National Guard, you will learn what you need to know to maintain, process, and troubleshoot military computer systems and operations.  The skills learned as an Information Technology Specialist can easily be transferred to the civilian workforce. You'll be able to work as a network support technician, data processing technician, or computer]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Army National Guard]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/31/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>ASHLAND</city>
        <state />
        <zip>36251</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157706428&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157706431</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Signal Support Systems Specialist]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication is the heartbeat of any Army National Guard unit. By joining the Army National Guard as a Signal Support Systems Specialist, you will keep the information flowing by making sure all communications equipment is in top working order. And while you maintain signal support devices and terminals in the Army National Guard, you will be building skills that will help you in your civilian career.  Signal Support Systems Specialists are responsible for integrating signal systems and networks; performing signal support functions and unit-level maintenance on authorized signal equipment; and installing, operating, and maintaining radio and data distribution systems. In]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Army National Guard]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/31/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>ASHLAND</city>
        <state />
        <zip>36251</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157706431&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157707176</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Signal Support Systems Specialist]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication is the heartbeat of any Army National Guard unit. By joining the Army National Guard as a Signal Support Systems Specialist, you will keep the information flowing by making sure all communications equipment is in top working order. And while you maintain signal support devices and terminals in the Army National Guard, you will be building skills that will help you in your civilian career.  Signal Support Systems Specialists are responsible for integrating signal systems and networks; performing signal support functions and unit-level maintenance on authorized signal equipment; and installing, operating, and maintaining radio and data distribution systems. In]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Army National Guard]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/31/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>TALLADEGA</city>
        <state />
        <zip>35161</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157707176&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157729266</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Java Developer  Strong J2EE application full life cycle development experience including specifying, building and deploying on Application servers and Web Services applications.  Experience in developing applications using Spring and Hibernate.  Strong Analysis experience, Domain Modeling, Use cases, Data Patterns, etc.  Strong relational Data Base knowledge/experiences such as Oracle/SQL Server database.  Programming in Java, J2EE, PL/SQL, SQL, XML, XSLT, Java Script  Experiences in Unix platform, Linux, Window NT, etc.  Experience with tools such as Eclipse, maven, ant, SVN, Jenkins  Ability to understand/pick up business domain knowledge within a short time period.  Good verbal communication. Good writing skills such as writing systems]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[CompSciPrep]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/01/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/30/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157729266&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157754126</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Solution Architect - ENOVIA]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Responsibilities:  · Leads account teams to understand client product development challenges.  · Leads the analysis, design, development and delivery of ENOVIA Solutions intended to address complex customer requirements, leveraging the ENOVIA product suite.  · Investigation and validation of current business processes to identify problems, complexities, non-value-added steps, and inefficient workflows that could be improved.  · Assigns tasks to project members and reviews teamwork work products to ensure that they are accurate and consistent.  · Proficient in prototyping solutions, using a broad range of ENOVIA 3DExperiences, Centrals, Industry Accelerators for client requirement gathering workshops, POC, and product presentations.  · Possesses expertise]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[AlphaNet Consulting]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/01/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/31/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157754126&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157884793</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Distribution Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Title: Distribution Analyst  ID: req6259  Type: Full Time  Function: Production / Distribution Support  Division: Motorparts - Aftermarket  Location: Jacksonville, AL, United States  ​Equal Opportunity Employer Minorities/Women/Veterans/Disabled  DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:  JOB TITLE: Distribution Analyst - Exempt Grade 305  LOCATION NAME: Jacksonville, AL  COUNTRY: U.S.  BUSINESS UNIT: Federal-Mogul Motorparts  REPORTS TO: Operations Support Manager  DEPARTMENT: Operations Support  JOB SUMMARY: Support operations, processes, data and other functional areas of Distribution. Plan and manage projects related to distribution and transportation. Coordinate the necessary support for these projects with other departments, including inventory, marketing, sales, and transportation.  RESPONSIBILITIES:  Follow all safety rules and regulations. Immediately]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Federal-Mogul Corporation]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/05/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/04/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Jacksonville</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>36265</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157884793&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158197695</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mumps Developer-100% Remote]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ideally candidates should have a Public Trust clearance, but at a minimum the candidate will need to be able to pass a Public Trust Clearance process.  Job Duties & Responsibilities  • We are seeking a Senior Developer to fill in a Sr. Mumps/Vista Developer role. Will report to and get directions from the Project Manager. Will provide development support including solution design, solution development, testing, delivery and deployment of the VistA enhancements. Will understand interface dependencies and ensure resolution of any issues pertaining to interfaces due to enhancements. Will utilize software development processes/standards of, or equivalent to, the Software Engineering]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Tallience]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/09/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/08/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158197695&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158417551</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[BUSINESS ANALYST/PROJECT MANAGER (PUBLIC SECTOR)]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUSINESS ANALYST/PROJECT MANAGER (PUBLIC SECTOR)  THE ROLE:  Sierra-Cedar Inc. is seeking an experienced BA/PM to lead the delivery of Justice & Public Safety and other state & local government IT integration projects in our national practice. You will develop and deliver project plans, define and document solution requirements, foster strong relationships with clients, and facilitate solutions to meet clients’ needs. You will possess a thorough understanding of fixed price deliverable based project structures and will harbor a broad business perspective in an IT and management consulting environment.  This role will require some travel to our client sites spread throughout the]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Sierra-Cedar]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/14/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/13/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158417551&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158513553</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[STRATEGIC STAFFING SOLUTIONS (S3) HAS AN OPENING!  S3 prides itself on being an international IT Staffing and Solutions company with 25 years’ experience recruiting and managing exceptional IT and Business consultants for customers in the Financial, Energy, Public Sector and Retail Distribution industries. We are a full service IT firm, with 25 major market locations and is a privately held, financially strong, woman owned company."  INTERVIEWING NOW! CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY!!!!  Know someone with your similar experience….  WE OFFER A $100.00 REFERRAL FEE FOR ANYONE REFERRED & HIRED WITH S3!  Strategic Staffing Solutions is currently searching for a Business Systems Analyst]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Strategic Staffing Solutions]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/15/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158513553&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158541903</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers and Architects ready to become Jedi Knights (250K+)]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[A Jedi Knight is someone adept in all areas of technology (from operating systems to algorithms) and shines when facing off with C-Level executives. An individual who is an expert at all phases of implementation and enjoys being hands on as much as possible!  How does one become a Jedi Knight?  1) Fantastic lightsaber fighting cabilities and plenty of experience developing complex Java/C++ platforms, applications, and tools.  2) A supreme interest in solving the problems of the universe. This big data/high performance product company is developing a user friendly platform ready to tackle major technical problems in any industry, from]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Gambit Technologies Inc]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/28/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158541903&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>159059613</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[.Net Software Engineer / Consultant]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[We are looking for a Sr. Software Consultant who will work as a part of a dynamic team in a rapidly growing organization. We are currently offering both Non-Travel (Virtual) and 75% Travel roles.  While the role is truly one of an individual contributor, a high degree of interaction and teamwork is required to be effective. Consultants within our Extended Services division operate fairly autonomously with minimal direct supervision. Team members in this role will work directly with clients and are expected to exercise sound judgment within defined best practices and always engage a client with the highest level of]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Momentum LLC]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/27/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/26/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=159059613&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>159118168</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[MongoDB Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[MongoDB Developer  DETAILS  Location: Remote  Position Type: 6+ Month Contract.  Salary Conversion: BOE  GTN Technical Staffing is searching for a MongoDB Engineer for a REMOTE contract role starting July 13, 2015. The company is located in San Diego but will allow the MongoBD Engineer to work from any location. This will be a 6+ month contract with extensions possible.  Technical Requirements:  2+ years of MongoDB Development  4+ years of Relational Database Development]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[GTN Technical Staffing - GoTechNow]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/28/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/27/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>323</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Anniston</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=159118168&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>152561833</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Programmer/Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is a rapidly growing operator of full-line sporting goods stores in small to mid-sized markets predominantly in the Southeast, Mid-Atlantic and Midwestern sections of the United States. Our stores offer a broad assortment of quality athletic equipment, footwear and apparel at competitive prices with superior customer service. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is the only sporting goods chain committed to serving small markets. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is based in Birmingham, Alabama with 1000+ stores operating in 32 states.  Hibbett Sports is now accepting applications for the position of Senior Programmer Analyst - AS400 Systems at its]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Hibbett Sports]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/26/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/25/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35211</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=152561833&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>152851715</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is a rapidly growing operator of full-line sporting goods stores in small to mid-sized markets predominantly in the Southeast, Mid-Atlantic and Midwestern sections of the United States. Our stores offer a broad assortment of quality athletic equipment, footwear and apparel at competitive prices with superior customer service. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is the only sporting goods chain committed to serving small markets. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is based in Birmingham, Alabama with 1000+ stores operating in 32 states.  Hibbett Sports is now accepting applications for the position of IT Senior Solutions Analyst - POS/Store Systems at]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Hibbett Sports]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/26/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/25/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35211</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=152851715&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>153261173</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Solutions Development Lead / McKesson]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Job ID: 57415  Title: Solutions Development Lead – McKesson STAR System  City, State: Birmingham,AL  Location: Virtual  Department: Finance Birmingham  Additional Job Details: FT, Days  Ascension Health (www.ascensionhealth.org) is transforming healthcare by providing the highest quality care to all, with special attention to those who are poor and vulnerable. Ascension Health, which provided $1.3 billion in care of persons living in poverty and community benefit programs last year, is the nation’s largest Catholic and nonprofit health system. Our Mission-focused Health Ministries employ more than 122,000 associates serving in more than 1,400 locations in 21 states and the District of Columbia.  Ascension]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Ascension Health Information Services]]></companyname>
      <activedate>09/04/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/03/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=153261173&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156732081</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Helpdesk Technician]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, A division of the Trimarc Group Inc., is searching for an experienced Helpdesk Technician (100% Phone Support).  This is a 6-month, contract-to-hire opportunity that will work on our client's 3:00pm to 11:00pm shift.  Essential Duties and Responsibilities:  Respond to alarm/trouble conditions within the Network Operations Center.  Troubleshooting the customer’s network and escalating to engineering and/or management.  Maintains knowledge of troubleshooting procedures and escalation paths.  Maintains appropriate records and documentation on service work performed and ensures timely communication to supervisor of service order status and potential issues.  Follow up on tickets at pre-defined intervals until resolved.  Ensure that problems]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/11/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/10/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156732081&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156820957</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Software Development Manager]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, A division of the Trimarc Group, Inc., is currently seeking a Software Development Manager to join a client in Birmingham, Alabama. This is a contract to permanent role that is immediately available.  This position will provide leadership and supervision to a small development team. The chosen candidate will provide work assignments and direction, ensure all timeline commitments are met and all related standards and policies are followed. This individual will plan, coordinate, and direct the activities of the software development team, as well as perform certain administrative activities as required. This is a hands-on position. In addition to]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/14/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/13/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156820957&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156826221</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Java Web Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., is currently seeking Java Web Developers with Single Page Applications (SPA) skills to develop Enterprise Level web applications for a rapidly growing client in Birmingham. AL. The candidates must be able to demonstrate an overall command of full SDLC development and show 3+ years of solid Java Web development. We are looking for candidates at all levels. These jobs are Direct-Hire positions and the salary is commensurate with experience.  Environment  Our client offers an exceptional workplace. They are very project focused, delivering the latest technologies in a rapid development environment. Everything]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/14/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/13/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156826221&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>156994178</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Business Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., has an immediate need for Business Analysts for one of our clients located in the Dothan, AL area. The role of the Business Analyst is in Business Process Modeling and Reengineering. The perfect candidates will help their clients to rethink how they work to improve service, cut costs and become world class organizations. This position will require a Secret Clearance or the ability to obtain an Interim Secret Clearance.  Roles and Responsibilities:  Perform business process modeling of current state and desired/future state processes  Evaluate current models and reengineer to produce greater]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/15/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Dothan</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>36301</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=156994178&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157117593</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Level 2 Software Engineer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Danieli Taranis is a full service supplier of Automation Systems for Raw Materials Handling, Melt Shops (EAF, LMF, VOD), Continuous Casters, Rolling Mills, Process Lines, Finishing Lines, Extrusion & Forging Plants.  We are seeking a dynamic and motivated Software Engineer at Danieli Taranis LLC who will be responsible for the design, development and implementation of process automation systems within the metals industry. The selected individual will report to the Software Engineering Manager while accountable for coding, debugging and implementing solutions by performing the following duties:  Duties and Responsibilities:  Design, code, test, debug, modify and refactor new and existing software using]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Danieli Taranis]]></companyname>
      <activedate>09/18/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/17/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157117593&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157279843</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Helpdesk Administrator]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., is currently searching for a Helpdesk Administrator for a permanent position for one of our clients in Birmingham, AL.  Qualified individuals must have experience in supporting technology issues ranging from PC software and applications, networking, security and connectivity. In this role, the individual will also be responsible for supporting escalations and will be provide mentoring and training to less experienced analysts.  Additional experience in ITIL processes and training is a plus.  Previous experience with implementation and administration of Helpdesk Software is highly desired as the organization will be transitioning to a]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/22/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/21/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157279843&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157284748</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Network Engineer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Professional Network Engineer  Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., has a direct-hire opportunity for a Network Engineer with solid Routing/Switching, Network Design/Implementation, Firewalls, VoIP, Security and Wireless experience in an Enterprise environment. This is a Direct-Hire position in the Birmingham, AL Metro Area.  Duties/Responsibilities:  Design/Develop/Test/Install Data and Voice Network  Design/Develop/Test/Install Communications Systems  Work with Business partners to manage plant cabling systems  Construction and IT project management  Design/Develop/Test/Install Client IT Security Infrastructure  Daily Tasks/Performed:  Prioritize and manage daily network errors and issues  Monitor and administer IT Security infrastructure  Work assigned IT projects in technical area  Train other IT]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/22/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/21/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157284748&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157442216</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Oracle DBA]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., has an immediate opening for a Oracle Database Administrator. The qualified candidate will have 5+ years experience with Oracle database administration.  Preferred Skills  Oracle Database Administration  Data Warehouse background  Oracle 10g, 11g ,12c  Oracle troubleshooting and problem resolution  Oracle database installations and upgrades  Oracle database performance tuning  Oracle database backup & recovery  Physical & logical database design  SQL & PL/SQL  In-depth knowledge of database technologies and tools, including Oracle and Informix  Some experience with Microsoft SQL Server  Very familiar with and experienced working with Dimensional Data Modeling  Experienced with Embarcadero’s ER/Studio]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/25/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/24/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157442216&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157442538</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[.NET Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., has an immediate permanent position fora mid-senior .NET Developer with knowledge of ASP.NET/C#/AJAX/XML/CSS/SQL Server and MVC4 to join our client in Birmingham, AL in the support, maintenance, and development of custom business applications.  Responsibilities  Develop web-based solutions for custom application requirements using standard approaches and using MVC  Work with business team and software developers in completing software enhancements  Develop reports using SSRS  Assist in testing and deployment of additional features and functionality that may include other object-oriented technologies  Provide various system administration functions  Required Technical Skills  Strong experience developing web-based applications]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/25/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/24/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157442538&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157443388</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, A division of the Trimarc Group Inc., is currently seeking a Programmer Analyst to join our client in Birmingham, Alabama.  Position Summary:  This position will work closely with other Analysts, the Manager of Infrastructure, as well as 3rd party development consultants.  The Information Technology Department manages the technology and computer infrastructure that drives the organization’s business systems. The IT department manages a network infrastructure that supports the headquarters office in Bessemer, AL as well as the offices located in Columbus, MS, Jackson, MS, Mobile, AL, Montgomery, AL, and Memphis, TN.  The Programmer Analyst position requires strong business skills]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/25/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/24/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157443388&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157454049</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[ETL Architect]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Precision Resources, a division of the Trimarc Group Inc., is currently seeking an ETL Architect to work in an Oracle Data Warehouse environment with one of our premiere clients in the Birmingham, AL Metro Area. The candidate must be able to demonstrate a command of Oracle Database development along with a strong knowledge of varied ETL tools.  Environment  Our client is consistently one of the best places to work in Birmingham. They are very employee focused and offer a wonderful, fast-paced environment conducive to teamwork, learning and the advancement of all the employees' skills. They are looking as much for]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Precision Resources]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/25/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/24/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157454049&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157459875</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Manager, IT Quality Assurance and Compliance]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is a rapidly growing operator of full-line sporting goods stores in small to mid-sized markets predominantly in the Southeast, Mid-Atlantic and Midwestern sections of the United States. Our stores offer a broad assortment of quality athletic equipment, footwear and apparel at competitive prices with superior customer service. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is the only sporting goods chain committed to serving small markets. Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc. is based in Birmingham, Alabama with 1000+ stores operating in 32 states.  Hibbett Sports is now accepting applications for the position of Manager, IT Quality Assurance and Compliance at its]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Hibbett Sports]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/26/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/25/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35211</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157459875&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157613038</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Entry Level Programmer/Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Black Creek Integrated Systems is a leading national supplier of integrated electronics security systems for the correctional industry. As a result of our experience and reputation in the corrections industry, Black Creek's technology has become a standard nationwide for many architectural and engineering firms specializing in criminal justice work.  We are seeking a qualified programmer/developer to work on the Criminal Justice Applications Group team.  Essential Duties & Responsibilities  Perform coding duties within a specified time frame  Provide assistance with software support and troubleshooting through interaction with the customer  Maintain proper coding practices and documentation, even under deadlines  Perform software quality]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Black Creek Integrated Systems]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/28/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35210</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157613038&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157669264</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Mid-Level MICROSOFT.NET SOFTWARE DEVELOPER]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Black Creek Integrated Systems is a leading national supplier of integrated electronics security systems for the correctional industry. As a result of our experience and reputation in the corrections industry, Black Creek's technology has become a standard nationwide for many architectural and engineering firms specializing in criminal justice work.  We are seeking a qualified software developer to work on the Criminal Justice Applications Group team.  Essential Duties & Responsibilities  Perform coding duties within a specified time frame  Provide assistance with software support and troubleshooting through interaction with the customer  Maintain proper coding practices and documentation, even under deadlines  Perform software]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Black Creek Integrated Systems]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/29/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35210</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157669264&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157669465</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[IT Web Applications Manager]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[We are Alpha1 Staffing/ Search Firm, a talent acquisition firm specializing providing workforce solutions ranging from small and medium businesses to the Fortune 500. We currently have a Applications Systems Analyst opportunity for an experienced IT Applications Manager for a healthcare benefits provider of ours in Birmingham, AL.  Position (Long-term Contract)  Candidate will act as a liaison to corporate IT and the client’s management in order to ensure business unit requests are complete and to ensure IT initiatives are completed timely and accurately.  Qualifications  · Bachelor degree required.  · Experience in a management position responsible for application development.  · Experience]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Alpha 1 Staffing]]></companyname>
      <activedate>09/30/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/30/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157669465&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157707072</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Signal Support Systems Specialist]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication is the heartbeat of any Army National Guard unit. By joining the Army National Guard as a Signal Support Systems Specialist, you will keep the information flowing by making sure all communications equipment is in top working order. And while you maintain signal support devices and terminals in the Army National Guard, you will be building skills that will help you in your civilian career.  Signal Support Systems Specialists are responsible for integrating signal systems and networks; performing signal support functions and unit-level maintenance on authorized signal equipment; and installing, operating, and maintaining radio and data distribution systems. In]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Army National Guard]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/29/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>10/31/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>ONEONTA</city>
        <state />
        <zip>35121</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157707072&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157794321</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[.NET Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Our client in Birmingham is looking for a .NET Developer to join their team. The primary responsibility of the .NET Developer will be to design and develop software and web pages for the company’s existing products. This individual must have experience using the following: JavaScript, HTML, VB.NET, C#, XML, SQL and CSS.  Candidates interested in this position, please send your resume to birmingham@southeasternit.com  ARG Financial Staffing/Southeastern Technology Consultants provides equal employment opportunities (EEO) to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, disability or genetics. In addition to federal law requirements, ARG]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Southeastern Technology Consultants]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157794321&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157796869</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Report Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Doozer Software's IT staffing division is currently assisting one of our clients in a search for a BI / Report Analyst. The BI/ Report Analyst will develop reports/dashboards using the BI tool Looker. This is a great opportunity to work with a new cutting edge report/dashboard. Our client has been in business over 15 years and has recently expanded into the Birmingham market so this is a great opportunity to get in on the ground floor of their new Birmingham office while working for an established company. Our customer develops/delivers Software as a Service products into a niche industry and]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Doozer]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/02/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35242</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157796869&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157798165</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Doozer Software’s IT staffing division is currently assisting one of our clients in a search for a Database Developer that will primarily develop Oracle PL/SQL packages from the ground up. This is a full time position that comes with an excellent suite of benefits and competitive salary. This role will initially start out on a project that is a rewrite of an existing application.  Requirements:  4+ years related hands-on experience with Oracle PL/SQL and Database technologies  Ability to develop Oracle PL/SQL packages from the ground up (Oracle 12c)  2+ years of Unix/Linux experience, preferably that includes writing shells scripts (Korn,]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Doozer]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/02/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35244</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157798165&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157801947</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Technology Director]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Technology Director  Job Label:Manager of Information Services  Education and/or Experience  All applicants must have a Bachelor’s degree or higher in MIS or equivalent related field; at least five years of experience in Information Systems or a related field; or equivalent combination of education and experience.  All applicants must have strong verbal and written communication skills, and must be able to read and comprehend instructions, correspondence, and memos in English. All applicants must have the ability to effectively present information in one-on-one and group situations.  Applicants must have strong analytical and problem solving skills and the ability to add, subtract, multiply,]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Milo's Tea Company]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/02/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Bessemer, AL</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35022</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157801947&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157802088</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Front End Web Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Southeastern Technology Consultants is working with a company in Birmingham, AL seeking a Front End Web Developer. This individual must have at least 3-5 years of experience.  Job Responsibilities:  - Plan, collaborate, and build efficient web interfaces with HTML, CSS, jQuery, and JavaScript  - Participate in design and code reviews  - Collaborate with other teams on the planning, development and execution of all design efforts  - Write code and run appropriate diagnostic tests to proactively solve potential issues  - Promote web standards, usability concepts and best practices  - Work with management to streamline the development process  If you are interested]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Southeastern Technology Consultants]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157802088&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157806862</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Java Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Doozer Software is currently assisting a client in a search for a Java Developer located downtown Birmingham, AL. This developer will join a team focused on producing user-focused software while working in an innovative and creative team environment. This developer will be involved in open platform projects and will be working for an innovative company that offers the opportunity to learn and develop.  Responsibilities:  Ability to work on multiple assignments and projects.  Anticipate future technical needs or problems.  Ability to learn new technologies as needed.  Ability to collaborate with cross-functional teams.  Job Requirements:  3+ years of Java Development experience  Agile/Scrum]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Doozer]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/02/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/01/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35242</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157806862&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157880146</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Java Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Our client is currently hiring Java Developers to customize their current proprietary platform while also interfacing with their customers directly. If you are a Developer that wants to stay current with bleeding edge technology, while also honing your customer interfacing skills, then this job is for you. These Engineers will implement the advanced Web-based enterprise solution software, for one of the fastest growing software companies in the region. Our client, offers a fully Web-based Java platform utilizing Web services and ACORD XML standards. They successfully leverage agile development methodology (using Scrum). You will be enhancing software, adding features, working with]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[ITAC Solutions]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/05/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/04/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city />
        <state />
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157880146&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>157898671</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[JOB SUMMARY  Are you looking for a challenging new software development experience where you can apply your creativity with pride and excellence? Join our team at Greenway Health! We are building the future of healthcare, developing cutting-edge health information technology (HIT) solutions to improve care delivery and to help create a smarter, more sustainable healthcare system. As we continue to grow, we are seeking a Software Developer.  You will excel in this role if you are able to apply your knowledge of information technology to solve real-world problems for our customers. This includes correcting issues in existing software and developing]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Greenway Health]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/05/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/04/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=157898671&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158312355</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[ASP.NET Developer - Industry Leading Medical Tech Company!]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[CyberCoders  Matching Great People with Great Companies  Learn more about CyberCoders  ASP.NET Developer  Apply  Birmingham, AL  Full-Time $75,000 - $80,000  Job Details  If you are a ASP.NET Developer with experience, please read on!  Top Reasons to Work with Us  We are an industry leading company in the medical technology and implant industry. With unique, progressive products backed by over 25 years of research, we continue to push the envelope in our field.  What You Will Be Doing  You will be utilizing the .NET stack to design, develop and implement software applications and components for both Windows and web-based applications, creating]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[CyberCoders]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/13/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/12/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35202</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158312355&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158322797</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Information Security Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Information Security Analyst  Rate: DOE  Duration: 6 months to a year  Mode of Interview: phone/skype  Client name/Domain: Confidential  Birmingham, AL  Position Title: Information Security Analyst (HIPAA)  Position Description:  Client is looking for Information Security Analyst (HIPAA) candidates for a position located in Birmingham, AL. Our client seeks to expand their team with the addition of an Information Security Analyst for a long term contract assignment. Under general direction, the incumbent will:  · Identify risks to information assets and data systems, ensuring compliance with industry standards, relevant regulations, and security best practices.  · Follow a risk-based approach to information security and]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Apetan Consulting LLC]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/27/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/12/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35201</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158322797&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158414583</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Systems Administrator #32390]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Systems Administrator  Bessemer, AL  If you are interested in this position, please email your resume to resumes2@nwexs.com. You may also text 248.707.1071 with your questions.  Job Description  Responsible for planning, installation, configuration, support and maintenance of organization's PC, laptops, servers, disaster recovery, and data centers. Ensure proper security measures are in place, high availability of servers and data storage for the enterprise. May occasionally supervise outside vendors to implement initiatives related to job responsibilities.  Plan, implement, monitor and provide support to ensure smooth and high uptime of all enterprise business systems by ensuring all servers, data storage and network systems]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Nationwide Technical & Executive Search, Inc]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/28/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/13/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Bessemer</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158414583&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158454569</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Sr. Cerner Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Job ID: 89867  Title: Senior Cerner Patient Management\HIM Analyst  City, State: Nashville, TN  Location: TNNAS 4515 - AHIS Office  Department: Finance Nashville  Additional Job Details: FT, Days  Ascension Health (www.ascensionhealth.org) is transforming healthcare by providing the highest quality care to all, with special attention to those who are poor and vulnerable. Ascension Health, which provided $1.3 billion in care of persons living in poverty and community benefit programs last year, is the nation’s largest Catholic and nonprofit health system. Our Mission-focused Health Ministries employ more than 122,000 associates serving in more than 1,400 locations in 21 states and the District]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Ascension Health Information Services]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/15/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>12/14/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158454569&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158478634</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[IT Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Position details:  Job Title: IT Analyst  Location: Birmingham, AL 35205  Duration: 6 plus months assignment which can get extended further basis on business needs and growth  Pay Rate: $36.00/hr. on W2.  Shift: Regular Shift  Job summary:  This position is responsible for providing data integration production/operations support and project work for the Generation business units. This position is responsible for working closely with the application developers, infrastructure department, team leads, and customers to ensure all data integration work assignments are completed with the highest level of quality and on time. The incumbent must ensure databases/systems are developed, maintained and operated to]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[TPI (Tech Providers, Inc.)]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/15/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/14/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35205</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158478634&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158541793</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer III]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[*This position is located on Kwajalein Atoll, in the Marshall Islands.  ESSENTIAL JOB DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:  · The Reagan Test Site (RTS) on Kwajalein, Republic of the Marshall Islands, incorporates a complex suite of sophisticated instrumentation that is used on a variety of ICBM re-entry, ICBM intercept, and space surveillance related missions in a real-time operational environment; the Mission Operations Software Engineer will focus on major and minor software improvements and will be developing software necessary to maintain and improve a variety of operational capabilities  · Primary responsibilities are centered on support of the RTS Distributed Operations (RDO) software as]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Kwajalein Range Services]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/15/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Kwajalein Atoll</city>
        <state />
        <zip>96555</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158541793&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158543109</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer/ IT Analyst]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Job Title: - IT Analyst  Duration:- 6+Months  Location: - Birmingham AL 35205  JOB SUMMARY:  This position is responsible for providing data integration production/operations support and project work for the Generation business units. This position is responsible for working closely with the application developers, infrastructure department, team leads, and customers to ensure all data integration work assignments are completed with the highest level of quality and on time. The incumbent must ensure databases/systems are developed, maintained and operated to attain high availability and business effectiveness. The scope of work includes: design, development, delivery, implementation and support of databases and associated data]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[TPI (Tech Providers, Inc.)]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/15/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35205</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158543109&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158545474</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[ON AIR HOST / DIGITAL ASSETS MANAGER]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Crawford Broadcasting Company in Birmingham, Alabama currently has an opening for a full-time On Air Host/Digital Assets Manager. This position requires that the On Air Host/Digital Assets Manager, manage the assets of the specified daypart(s). Asset management includes any aspect of the daypart which would need to be made different from or better than any other competing daypart. The requirement of the host is to extract maximum value from those assets. The most critical aspect of asset management is for the host to aggressively sell every element contained in the daypart.  In addition this position would require management of local]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[Crawford Broadcasting Company]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/16/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/15/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35209</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158545474&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158623744</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Developer - ASP MVC]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[DescriptionAllstates Consulting Services is seeking a Senior Front-End Developer - ASP MVC for a Full time position with an excellent company and long-term client in Birmingham, AL.  Seeking someone with:  Excellent communication skills  3+ years development experience  3 years (minimum) with .NET framework  Specify versions of .NET framework developed under  ASP.NET  MVC 4 or 5  HTML5 & CSS3  SQL Server 2008+  Eagerness to learn:  Responsive design  Message Queuing/AMQP knowledge  OAuth 2  NServiceBus v4+  MongoDB  WebSphere  MessageBroker  Distributed and Asynchronous Design and Development strongly preferred  tags: asp, mvc, .net, c#, developer, html, css, javascript, angular, nosql, sql, programmer, engineer]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[AllStates Consulting]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/19/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/18/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35223</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158623744&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
    <job>
      <adid />
      <jobid>158632454</jobid>
      <title><![CDATA[Web Developer, Project Manager, Web Technologies]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Web Developer, Project Manager, Web Technologies  Job Label:MAG_1508157EA68  Lead and Manage DataPerk Web Projects. Utilize web technologies to meet the requirements of DataPerk customers in order to finish projects on time, on budget and without defect.  Responsibilities include the following (Other duties may be assigned):  Work closely with clients, project managers, and other members of the development team to both develop detailed specification documents with clear project deliverables and timelines, and to ensure timely completion of deliverables.  Manage workflow of web department and utilize the ticketing functionality within AutoTask to track time and make notes on accounts and projects.  Produce]]></description>
      <companyname><![CDATA[DataPerk]]></companyname>
      <activedate>10/19/2015</activedate>
      <expiresdate>11/18/2015</expiresdate>
      <jobboardid>1</jobboardid>
      <xcode />
      <locationid>324</locationid>
      <physicallocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip>35233</zip>
        <country>US</country>
      </physicallocation>
      <targetlocation>
        <city>Birmingham</city>
        <state>AL</state>
        <zip />
        <country>US</country>
      </targetlocation>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <applyurl>http://clk.atdmt.com/MON/go/398763636/direct/01/?h=http://anuncio-emprego.monster.com.br/getjob.aspx?JobId=158632454&amp;jvs=cf,can-7144,can,0&amp;WT.mc_n=olm_sk_feed_samplefeed</applyurl>
      <categoryids>
        <category>
          <Categoryid>660</Categoryid>
          <CategoryName>IT/Software Development</CategoryName>
        </category>
      </categoryids>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</monsterfeed>
